labdoor.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy - LabDoor

Welcome to LabDoor, a registered DBA of Labrdr Inc. (hereafter referred to as "LabDoor", "we", or "our"). LabDoor is developed and designed to help consumers learn more about the price, safety, and efficacy of their current and potential products. Please read this agreement carefully before using LabDoor. 

LabDoor takes your privacy very seriously. We understand how important it is to our users, and we will never misuse our users' trust in this or any other matter. This policy covers the LabDoor website ("Site"), its mobile applications ("Apps"), software, APIs, data services, and all Content (Collectively the "Services"). 

This document (the "Privacy Policy") sets forth our practices and policies in respect to our collection, use, and sharing of personal information through your use of the Services: 

##  PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION 

By submitting personally identifiable information ("PII") through our Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the processing of your PII in accordance with our Privacy Policy. Please do not use the Services if you do not want the Privacy Policy to apply to you. 

We may collect PII about you, such as your name, date of birth, gender, address, email address, health information, or product usage, in the following ways: 

  * When you register for or update your profile on our Apps and/or Site.
  * When you sign up for newsletters or other communications from LabDoor.
  * When you participate in surveys, product reviews, or community/blog discussions.
  * When you connect with LabDoor through social media outlets, such as Facebook and Twitter.

##  AGGREGATE INFORMATION 

We may also collect aggregate information about our users, including demographic and usage information about our Services. This information may be shared with our partners, including shareholders and advertisers. This information will never identify individual users nor be linked with PII. 

##  YOUR CHOICE 

If you wish to not share PII with LabDoor as provided in this Privacy Policy, please do not register as a member on this Site or Apps or enter any information into the public sections of our Services. If you choose to enter into this agreement and use our Services, you may correct, update, or review any PII you have submitted by signing into our Services and updating your registration and/or profile information. You may also delete your information, as provided by our Services. 

##  WEB TRACKING 

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. "Web beacons" are graphic image files imbedded in a web page typically used to monitor activity on a web page and send back to its home server. Web beacons may also be used on this site. 

LabDoor does not link the information we store in cookies or web beacons to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site and to provide you with enhanced services (viewing history, account information). A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. If you reject cookies, you can still use our site, but your ability to use or access some areas of our site may be limited. If you choose to reject Cookies, you may by utilizing one of the many browser software options that include this option. LabDoor may utilize these web tracking features to help tailor advertising, advice, and alerts to you. 

##  MOBILE APPLICATIONS 

When you download and install one of our Apps, we may provide a random ID number to your installation. This number is not linked to any PII. It is used similarly to our web tracking tools, as described in our Privacy Policy, to help improve our Services. If you choose not to use this ID number during your use of LabDoor's services, please opt out of using our Apps, and instead access LabDoor services through a mobile browser. 

##  HOW PII IS USED 

We may use the information we collect about you to: 

  * To comply with applicable laws and legal action, including local, state, federal, and/or international regulations.
  * When we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect the rights of LabDoor and/or the users of our Services.
  * In the event of pending or official corporate change of control, or the addition of any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies controlled by the same entity as LabDoor.
  * In order to provide you with our Services, we may need to share your PII with our third party service providers. These service providers are required to utilize your PII only in ways authorized by LabDoor.

##  SHARING PII 

LabDoor will never disclose any PII related to you unless specifically agreed to by you or: 

  * To comply with applicable laws and legal action, including local, state, federal, and/or international regulations.
  * When we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect the rights of LabDoor and/or the users of our Services.
  * In the event of pending or official corporate change of control, or the addition of any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies controlled by the same entity as LabDoor.
  * In order to provide you with our Services, we may need to share your PII with our third party service providers. These service providers are required to utilize your PII only in ways authorized by LabDoor.

##  SECURITY 

We administer numerous physical, technical, and administrative safeguards to protect any PII that we collect from you. We will strive to provide the most secure transfer of information at all times; however, we cannot guarantee its absolute security at all times. If you feel that your information security has been jeopardized in any way, please contact [contact@labdoor.com](mailto:contact@labdoor.com) immediately. 

##  COMMUNICATIONS FROM LABDOOR 

In order to provide you with our Services, we may contact you using the information that you have provided to LabDoor. These communications may include: 

  * Customer Service Activities: This may include emails, letters, and/or packages meant to welcome you to our Services, provide you with Services, thank you for being a user, help manage your account, update your PII, or respond to your inquiries.
  * Service Announcements: On rare occasions, we may send you information about our Services, including emails, letters, and/or packages to describe new Services, publicize changes to existing Services, explain disruptions to our services, or to announce key news related to LabDoor.

##  DATA RETENTION 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact [contact@labdoor.com](mailto:contact@labdoor.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements 

##  CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY 

If at any time LabDoor decides to change our privacy practices, a revised edition of this Privacy Policy will be posted to our Site, and to any other places within our Services where we deem appropriate, in order to help our users understand our policies. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. 

##  QUESTIONS 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact [contact@labdoor.com](mailto:contact@labdoor.com).
